<resources>
    <string name="app_name">StorIT</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="pass">Password</string>
    <string name="forgotPass">Forgot Password\?</string>
    <string name="login">Log In</string>
    <string name="signUpGoogle">Sign Up with Google</string>

    <string name="titleForSignUp">Join the \nCommunity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="empty_fragment_string">There\'s nothing here!</string>

    <string name="termsAndCondition">
        Last updated: 10-10-2019 \n
        Please read these Terms and Conditions carefully before using
        the <b>http://www.CyberMonkeys.com</b> website and StorIT mobile
application (the "Service") operated by CyberMonkeys.
Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on your acceptance of and compliance with
these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users and others who access or use the Service.\n\n

        If you wish to purchase any product or service made available through the Service ("Purchase"),
you may be asked to supply certain information relevant to your Purchase including, without
limitation, your …
The Purchases section is for businesses that sell online (physical or digital). For the full
disclosure section, create your own Terms and Conditions. \n\n

        Some parts of the Service are billed on a subscription basis ("Subscription(s)"). You will be billed in
advance on a recurring …
The Subscriptions section is for SaaS businesses. For the full disclosure section, create your
own Terms and Conditions. \n\n

        Our Service allows you to post, link, store, share and otherwise make available certain information,
text, graphics, videos, or other material ("Content"). You are responsible for the …
The Content section is for businesses that allow users to create, edit, share, make content on
their websites or apps. For the full disclosure section, create your own Terms and Conditions. \n\n

        Our Service may contain links to third-party web sites or services that are not owned or controlled
by StorIT. CyberMonkeys has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content,
privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or services. You further acknowledge and
agree that My Company (change this) shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any
damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any
such content, goods or services available on or through any such web sites or services.\n\n

        We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a
revision is material we will try to provide at least 30 (change this) days\' notice prior to any new terms
taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.\n\n

        If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us.
    </string>

    <string-array name="region">
        <item>AP</item>
        <item>EU</item>
        <item>ME</item>
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>OC</item>
        <item>SA</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="months">
        <item>Month</item>
        <item>01</item>
        <item>02</item>
        <item>03</item>
        <item>04</item>
        <item>05</item>
        <item>06</item>
        <item>07</item>
        <item>08</item>
        <item>09</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>11</item>
        <item>12</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="years">
        <item>Year</item>
        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2020</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
